<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20161006</CreaDate><CreaTime>16243700</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><ArcGISstyle>FGDC CSDGM Metadata</ArcGISstyle><SyncOnce>FALSE</SyncOnce><DataProperties><itemProps><itemName Sync="TRUE">BighornOwnerParcel_shp</itemName><itemLocation><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://\\MSLGEOINFO2516\C$\Cadastral\Production\Bighorn\BighornOwnerParcel_shp.shp</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></itemLocation><nativeExtBox><westBL Sync="TRUE">111848.620000</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">1030197.650000</eastBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">17695.160000</southBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">547983.680000</northBL><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode></nativeExtBox><imsContentType Sync="TRUE">002</imsContentType><itemSize Sync="TRUE">0.000</itemSize></itemProps><coordRef><type Sync="TRUE">Projected</type><geogcsn Sync="TRUE">GCS_North_American_1983</geogcsn><csUnits Sync="TRUE">Linear Unit: Meter (1.000000)</csUnits><projcsn Sync="TRUE">NAD_1983_StatePlane_Montana_FIPS_2500</projcsn><peXml Sync="TRUE">&lt;ProjectedCoordinateSystem xsi:type='typens:ProjectedCoordinateSystem' xmlns:xsi='http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance' xmlns:xs='http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema' xmlns:typens='http://www.esri.com/schemas/ArcGIS/10.5'&gt;&lt;WKT&gt;PROJCS[&amp;quot;NAD_1983_StatePlane_Montana_FIPS_2500&amp;quot;,GEOGCS[&amp;quot;GCS_North_American_1983&amp;quot;,DATUM[&amp;quot;D_North_American_1983&amp;quot;,SPHEROID[&amp;quot;GRS_1980&amp;quot;,6378137.0,298.257222101]],PRIMEM[&amp;quot;Greenwich&amp;quot;,0.0],UNIT[&amp;quot;Degree&amp;quot;,0.0174532925199433]],PROJECTION[&amp;quot;Lambert_Conformal_Conic&amp;quot;],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;False_Easting&amp;quot;,600000.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;False_Northing&amp;quot;,0.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Central_Meridian&amp;quot;,-109.5],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Standard_Parallel_1&amp;quot;,45.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Standard_Parallel_2&amp;quot;,49.0],PARAMETER[&amp;quot;Latitude_Of_Origin&amp;quot;,44.25],UNIT[&amp;quot;Meter&amp;quot;,1.0],AUTHORITY[&amp;quot;EPSG&amp;quot;,32100]]&lt;/WKT&gt;&lt;XOrigin&gt;-35666000&lt;/XOrigin&gt;&lt;YOrigin&gt;-30006900&lt;/YOrigin&gt;&lt;XYScale&gt;124182419.54917815&lt;/XYScale&gt;&lt;ZOrigin&gt;-100000&lt;/ZOrigin&gt;&lt;ZScale&gt;10000&lt;/ZScale&gt;&lt;MOrigin&gt;-100000&lt;/MOrigin&gt;&lt;MScale&gt;10000&lt;/MScale&gt;&lt;XYTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/XYTolerance&gt;&lt;ZTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/ZTolerance&gt;&lt;MTolerance&gt;0.001&lt;/MTolerance&gt;&lt;HighPrecision&gt;true&lt;/HighPrecision&gt;&lt;WKID&gt;32100&lt;/WKID&gt;&lt;LatestWKID&gt;32100&lt;/LatestWKID&gt;&lt;/ProjectedCoordinateSystem&gt;</peXml></coordRef><lineage><Process ToolSource="c:\program files (x86)\arcgis\desktop10.5\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Analysis Tools.tbx\Select" Date="20190411" Time="075805">Select C:\Cadastral\Processing\StatewideParcel.gdb\OwnerParcel C:\Cadastral\Processing\Bighorn.mdb\ParcelFeatures\OwnerParcel "COUNTYCD = 22"</Process><Process ToolSource="c:\program files (x86)\arcgis\desktop10.5\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\CopyFeatures" Date="20190411" Time="075819">CopyFeatures C:\Cadastral\Processing\Bighorn.mdb\ParcelFeatures\OwnerParcel C:\Cadastral\Production\Bighorn\BighornOwnerParcel_shp.shp # 0 0 0</Process></lineage></DataProperties><SyncDate>20190411</SyncDate><SyncTime>07581400</SyncTime><ModDate>20190411</ModDate><ModTime>07581400</ModTime><ArcGISProfile>FGDC</ArcGISProfile><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange></Esri><mdLang><languageCode value="eng"/><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"/></mdLang><mdChar><CharSetCd value="004"/></mdChar><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv><mdContact><rpOrgName>Montana State Library</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntPhone><voiceNum>406-444-5354</voiceNum><voiceNum tddtty="True">406-444-4799</voiceNum><faxNum>406-444-0266</faxNum></cntPhone><cntAddress addressType="postal"><delPoint>P.O. Box 201800</delPoint><city>Helena</city><adminArea>Montana</adminArea><postCode>59620</postCode><eMailAdd>geoinfo@mt.gov</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntHours>8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.</cntHours></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="007"/></role></mdContact><mdDateSt Sync="FALSE">20190410</mdDateSt><mdStanName>ArcGIS Metadata</mdStanName><mdStanVer>1.0</mdStanVer><distInfo><distributor><distorCont><rpOrgName>Montana State Library</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntPhone><voiceNum>406-444-5354</voiceNum><voiceNum tddtty="True">406-444-4799</voiceNum><faxNum>406-444-0266</faxNum></cntPhone><cntAddress addressType="postal"><delPoint>P.O. Box 201800</delPoint><city>Helena</city><adminArea>MT</adminArea><postCode>59620</postCode><eMailAdd>geoinfo@mt.gov</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntHours>8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.</cntHours></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="005"/></role></distorCont></distributor><distTranOps><onLineSrc><linkage>http://ftp.geoinfo.msl.mt.gov/Data/Spatial/MSDI/Cadastral/Parcels/</linkage></onLineSrc><transSize Sync="TRUE">0.000</transSize></distTranOps><distFormat><formatName Sync="TRUE">Shapefile</formatName></distFormat></distInfo><dataIdInfo><idCitation><date><pubDate>2019-04-10T00:00:00</pubDate></date><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Montana State Library</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntAddress><delPoint>Helena, MT</delPoint></cntAddress></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="010"/></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Montana Department of Revenue</rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Missoula County</rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Montana State Library</rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Flathead County</rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Yellowstone County</rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Ravalli County</rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role></citRespParty><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Silver Bow County</rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role></citRespParty><presForm><PresFormCd value="005"/></presForm><presForm><fgdcGeoform>vector digital data</fgdcGeoform></presForm><otherCitDet>Online linkage is for the individual county databases. Statewide databases can be found at ftp://ftp.geoinfo.msl.mt.gov/Data/Spatial/MSDI/Cadastral/Parcels/Statewide</otherCitDet><resTitle Sync="TRUE">BighornOwnerParcel_shp</resTitle></idCitation><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The Montana Cadastral Framework shows the taxable parcels and tax-exempt parcels for most of Montana. The parcels contain selected information such as owner names, property and owner addresses, assessed value, agricultural use, and tax district information that were copied from the Montana Department of Revenue's ORION tax appraisal database. The data are maintained by the MT Department of Revenue, except for Ravalli, Silver Bow, Missoula, Flathead, and Yellowstone counties that are maintained by the individual counties. The Revenue and county data are integrated by Montana State Library staff. Each parcel contains an attribute called ParcelID (geocode) that is the parcel identifier. Large areas of public land in Flathead County are missing from the data. The parcel boundaries were aligned to fit with the Bureau of Land Management Geographic Coordinate Database (GCDB) of public land survey coordinates. Parcels whose legal descriptions consisted of aliquot parts of the public land survey system were created from the GCDB coordinates by selecting and, when necessary, subdividing public land survey entities. Other parcels were digitized from paper maps and the data from each map were transformed to fit with the appropriate GCDB boundaries.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idPurp>Land ownership information that is tied to the Montana Department of Revenue's ORION database and available for a variety of mapping and query purposes.</idPurp><idCredit>The data were made possible by a public/private partnership including the U.S. Bureau of Land Management, several state agencies, local governments, The Montana Power Company, Montana/Dakota Utilities, and Burlington Northern Sante Fe Railroad. Most data are being maintained by staff of the Montana Department of Revenue (DOR).</idCredit><idStatus><ProgCd value="007"/></idStatus><idPoC><rpOrgName>Montana State Library</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntPhone><voiceNum>406-444-5354</voiceNum><voiceNum tddtty="True">406-444-4799</voiceNum><faxNum>406-444-0266</faxNum></cntPhone><cntAddress addressType="postal"><delPoint>P.O. Box 201800</delPoint><city>Helena</city><adminArea>Montana</adminArea><postCode>59620</postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>geoinfo@mt.gov</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntHours>8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.</cntHours><cntInstr>e-mail contact is preferred</cntInstr></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="007"/></role></idPoC><resMaint><maintFreq><MaintFreqCd value="001"/></maintFreq></resMaint><placeKeys><keyword>Montana</keyword></placeKeys><themeKeys><keyword>MSDI</keyword><keyword>Montana Spatial Data Infrastructure</keyword><keyword>Tax Parcel</keyword><keyword>Cadastral</keyword></themeKeys><themeKeys><thesaName><resTitle>ISO 19115 Topic Category</resTitle></thesaName><keyword>planningCadastre</keyword><keyword>boundaries</keyword></themeKeys><searchKeys><keyword>MSDI</keyword><keyword>planningCadastre</keyword><keyword>Montana Spatial Data Infrastructure</keyword><keyword>boundaries</keyword><keyword>Tax Parcel</keyword><keyword>Montana</keyword><keyword>Cadastral</keyword></searchKeys><resConst><LegConsts><useLimit>This data is a cooperative effort between the Montana State Libary and the Montana Department of Revenue (DOR) other state agencies, local, governments, USDI BLM and private enterprise. The MSL provides mapped cadastral data, Web development, deployment, and enhancements. The DOR provides maintenance as well as CAMA data relating to the mapped cadastral data. Neither the MSL nor any associated partner, nor their employees, makes any warranty, expressed or implied, including the fitness for a particular purpose, or assumes any legal liability responsibility for the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of any information, apparatus, product, or process disclosed, or represents that its use would not infringe privately owned rights. In layman's terms: the data not constitute a legal survey; inaccuracies exist with both the mapped data and the CAMA data; when seeking the definitive description of real property, consult the deed recorded at the local county courthouse. State law ( Montana Code Annotated 2-6-109 (1)(a) ) explicitly prohibits State agencies from selling or distributing a list of persons to be used as a mailing list without first securing the permission of those on the list. State law ( MCA 2-6-109 (1)(b) ) also explicitly prohibits anyone from using a list of persons prepared by a state agency as a mailing list without first securing the permission of those on the list. "A person violating the provisions of subsection (1)(b) is guilty of a misdemeanor."</useLimit></LegConsts></resConst><resConst><Consts><useLimit>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;State law (Montana Code Annotated 2-6-1017) prohibits anyone from using a list of persons prepared by a public agency as a distribution list without first securing the permission of those on the list. &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;A person violating the provisions of subsection (1)(b) is guilty of a misdemeanor.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;These data do not constitute a legal survey. Inaccuracies exist with both the parcel boundaries and the attribute data; when seeking the definitive description of real property, consult the deed recorded at the local county courthouse. The Montana State Library provides this product/service for informational purposes only. The Library did not produce it for, nor is it suitable for legal, engineering, or surveying purposes. Consumers of this information should review or consult the primary data and information sources to ascertain the viability of the information for their purposes. The Library provides these data in good faith but does not represent or warrant its accuracy, adequacy, or completeness. In no event shall the Library be liable for any incorrect results or analysis; any direct, indirect, special, or consequential damages to any party; or any lost profits arising out of or in connection with the use or the inability to use the data or the services provided. The Library makes these data and services available as a convenience to the public, and for no other purpose. The Library reserves the right to change or revise published data and/or services at any time.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</useLimit></Consts></resConst><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd value="001"/></spatRpType><dataLang><languageCode value="eng"/><countryCode value="USA" Sync="TRUE"/></dataLang><dataExt><exDesc>publication date</exDesc><tempEle><TempExtent><exTemp><TM_Instant><tmPosition>2019-04-10T00:00:00</tmPosition></TM_Instant></exTemp></TempExtent></tempEle></dataExt><dataExt><geoEle><GeoBndBox><westBL>-116.178571</westBL><eastBL>-103.611177</eastBL><southBL>44.23772</southBL><northBL>49.180871</northBL></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt><dataChar><CharSetCd value="004"/></dataChar><envirDesc Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows 7 Version 6.1 (Build 7601) Service Pack 1; Esri ArcGIS 10.5.1.7333</envirDesc><dataExt><geoEle><GeoBndBox esriExtentType="search"><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode><westBL Sync="TRUE">-116.178571</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">-103.611130</eastBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">49.180871</northBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">44.237720</southBL></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt><tpCat><TopicCatCd value="015"/></tpCat><tpCat><TopicCatCd value="017"/></tpCat><tpCat><TopicCatCd value="003"/></tpCat></dataIdInfo><mdMaint><maintFreq><MaintFreqCd value="005"/></maintFreq></mdMaint><dqInfo><dqScope><scpLvl><ScopeCd value="005"/></scpLvl></dqScope><report type="DQConcConsis"><measDesc>Databases checked for standardization</measDesc></report><report type="DQCompOm"><measDesc>There are known unresolved parcels in some townships. As township level metadata becomes available these known ommissions will be documented. Until then the data should be considered 99 percent complete.</measDesc></report><report type="DQQuanAttAcc"><measDesc>Attributes were complete when returned to ISD from vendor (see data creation process in process steps). We can not verify that these attributes will remain complete when the data is in maintenance.</measDesc></report><report type="DQAbsExtPosAcc" dimension="horizontal"><measDesc>Please refer to the GCDB reference in the abstract. The data can't be more accurate than the GCDB township from which it was developed. Positional accuracy of GCDB townships vary based on the number and quality of surveys and control points. To find the positional accuracy of a GCDB township, one can download the file from their website and examine the .pgc file.</measDesc></report><dataLineage><prcStep><stepDesc>This is the process used in most counties. Some counties had existing data and different processes were followed. Contact Missoula, Yellowstone, Butte-Silver Bow, Ravalli, or Flathead for information on the processes used by those counties. A small percentage of Montana's are subdivided, leaving a large percentage of land in aliquot parts. Because aliquot parts are a mathematical subdivision of larger parcels into smaller equally-sized smaller parcels it is possible to possible to create ownership parcels in an automated manner, if the supporting data exists. Two pieces of information are required create aliquot part parcels: 1) legal land descriptions defining the aliquot parts to plot and 2) framework of coordinates defining the public land survey. Both pieces of information exist, for most of the State of Montana, in a digital format. These existing databases are the Montana Department of Revenue Computer Assisted Mass Appraisal System (CAMA) database and the U.S. Bureau of Land Management Geographic Coordinate Data Base (GCDB). CAMA is a database of all taxable (and some tax-exempt) lands in the State of Montana. It has four 30-character text fields for legal land descriptions of property. The GCDB holds locational information (x/y coordinates) of all section, quarter section, and quarter-quarter section corners, by township. Integrating the above two databases to produce digital land ownership parcels requires custom written software. This suite of programs, called the Montana Automated Parcel Program (MAPP), is the backbone of the Project. Vendors on contract with the cadastral project filled in unmapped areas, or 'holes', which remain in a township after running MAPP. These 'holes' are filled after field research at county courthouses which yields information about deeds, certificates of survey, and paper maps. Vendors also use a file generated by MAPP listing all parcels from the CAMA database not mapped during the automated process. General Process: -- Download GCDB -- Download DOR CAMA file -- Process aliquot parts using MAPP software -- Proof maps -- Identify missing parcels -- Send missing parcels to vendor -- Vendor researchs missing parcels -- Vendor converts missing parcels -- qa/qc -- database checked for consistancy -- identify unresolved parcels -- if under 5% all parcels to convert vendor work done -- DOR researched unresolved parcels -- DOR or GIS Bureau converts remaining unresolved parcels</stepDesc><stepDateTm date="inapplicable"/><stepProc><rpIndName>Montana State Library</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Montana State Library</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntPhone><voiceNum>406-444-5354</voiceNum><faxNum>406-444-0266</faxNum></cntPhone><cntAddress><eMailAdd>geoinfo@mt.gov</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntHours>8:00 a.m. to 5:00 p.m.</cntHours></rpCntInfo><role><RoleCd value="009"/></role></stepProc></prcStep><dataSource><srcCitatn><resTitle>Montana Department of Revenue Orion (CAMA) data</resTitle><resAltTitle>Montana Department of Revenue Orion (CAMA) data</resAltTitle><citRespParty><rpOrgName>Montana Department of Revenue</rpOrgName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role></citRespParty></srcCitatn></dataSource></dataLineage></dqInfo><eainfo><detailed Name="BighornOwnerParcel_shp"><enttyp><enttypl Sync="TRUE">BighornOwnerParcel_shp</enttypl><enttypd>Taxable land parcel as defined by MT. Dept. of Revenue and the Counties</enttypd><enttypds>MSL, DOR, counties</enttypds><enttypt Sync="TRUE">Feature Class</enttypt><enttypc Sync="TRUE">0</enttypc></enttyp><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FID</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">OID</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">4</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>GISAcres</attrlabl><attrdef>Software Calculated Acreage</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">GISAcres</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>OwnerState</attrlabl><attrdef>The two-character abbreviation of the state of the taxpayer's mailing address</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">OwnerState</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">2</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>PropAccess</attrlabl><attrdef>List of codes for type of road or other access to the property</attrdef><attrdomv><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>dirt road</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>seasonal access</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>alley</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>paved road</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>sidewalk</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>semi-improved road</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>proposed road</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>0</edomv><edomvd>landlocked/none</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>railroad</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>9</edomv><edomvd>river/waterway</edomvd></edom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="TRUE">PropAccess</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">40</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>OwnerCity</attrlabl><attrdef>name of the city or town of the taxpayer's mailing address</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">OwnerCity</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">40</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>TaxYear</attrlabl><attrdef>Tax year for which information is relevant</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">TaxYear</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Integer</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">10</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Section_</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Section_</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Assessment</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Assessment</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">20</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>TotalAcres</attrlabl><attrdef>Total acres of the parcel. In some areas this is filled out only for parcels that have agricultural acreage listed</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">TotalAcres</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>Township</attrlabl><attrdef>Township (N or S) that the property is located in</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">Township</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>COUNTYCD</attrlabl><attrdef>county code</attrdef><attrdomv><edom><edomv>54</edomv><edomvd>Mineral County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>44</edomv><edomvd>Wheatland County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>20</edomv><edomvd>Valley County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>31</edomv><edomvd>Teton County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>26</edomv><edomvd>Pondera County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>47</edomv><edomvd>Meagher County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>23</edomv><edomvd>Musselshell County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>42</edomv><edomvd>Carter County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>18</edomv><edomvd>Beaverhead County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>50</edomv><edomvd>Garfield County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>48</edomv><edomvd>Liberty County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>45</edomv><edomvd>Prairie County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>35</edomv><edomvd>Sanders County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>32</edomv><edomvd>Stillwater County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>8</edomv><edomvd>Fergus County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>43</edomv><edomvd>Broadwater County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>5</edomv><edomvd>Lewis and Clark County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>51</edomv><edomvd>Jefferson County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>4</edomv><edomvd>Missoula County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>53</edomv><edomvd>Golden Valley County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>39</edomv><edomvd>Falon County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>19</edomv><edomvd>Choteau County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>2</edomv><edomvd>Cascade County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>56</edomv><edomvd>Lincoln County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>36</edomv><edomvd>Judith Basin County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>55</edomv><edomvd>Petroleum County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>25</edomv><edomvd>Madison County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>52</edomv><edomvd>Wibaux County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>22</edomv><edomvd>Big Horn County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>15</edomv><edomvd>Lake County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>9</edomv><edomvd>Powder River County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>41</edomv><edomvd>McCone County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>37</edomv><edomvd>Daniels County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>29</edomv><edomvd>Rosebud County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>24</edomv><edomvd>Blaine County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>13</edomv><edomvd>Ravalli County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>14</edomv><edomvd>Custer County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>7</edomv><edomvd>Flathead County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>11</edomv><edomvd>Phillips County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>46</edomv><edomvd>Granite County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>34</edomv><edomvd>Sheridan County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>40</edomv><edomvd>Sweet Grass County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>6</edomv><edomvd>Gallatin County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>21</edomv><edomvd>Toole County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>38</edomv><edomvd>Glacier County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>1</edomv><edomvd>Silver Bow County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>28</edomv><edomvd>Powell County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>16</edomv><edomvd>Dawson County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>27</edomv><edomvd>Richland County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>33</edomv><edomvd>Treasure County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>17</edomv><edomvd>Roosevelt County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>49</edomv><edomvd>Park County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>10</edomv><edomvd>Carbon County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>3</edomv><edomvd>Yellowstone County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>30</edomv><edomvd>Deer Lodge County</edomvd></edom><edom><edomv>12</edomv><edomvd>Hill County</edomvd></edom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="TRUE">COUNTYCD</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Integer</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">5</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">5</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">LegalDescr</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">LegalDescr</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">160</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Subdivisio</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Subdivisio</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">60</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Certificat</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Certificat</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">30</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">AddressLin</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">AddressLin</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">104</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">AddressL_1</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">AddressL_1</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">27</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">CityStateZ</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">CityStateZ</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">55</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>Range</attrlabl><attrdef>Township range (E or W) that the property is located in</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">Range</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">LevyDistri</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">LevyDistri</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">81</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>OwnerName</attrlabl><attrdef>This is the name of the parcel owner</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">OwnerName</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">167</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">Continuous</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">Continuous</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FallowAcre</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FallowAcre</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">FarmsiteAc</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">FarmsiteAc</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">ForestAcre</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">ForestAcre</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">GrazingAcr</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">GrazingAcr</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">WildHayAcr</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">WildHayAcr</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">IrrigatedA</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">IrrigatedA</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">NonQualAcr</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">NonQualAcr</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl><attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef><attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Geometry</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">0</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">TotalBuild</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">TotalBuild</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Integer</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">10</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">TotalLandV</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">TotalLandV</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Integer</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">10</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>PARCELID</attrlabl><attrdef>Feature Parcel identifier number (geocode)</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">PARCELID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">17</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>PropType</attrlabl><attrdef>Property type</attrdef><attrdomv><edom><edomv>IR - Industrial Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>MC - Mining Claims</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>MU - Mixed Use / Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>BR - Commercial Condo Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>EP - Exempt Property</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>VR - Vacant Land Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>AR - Agricultural Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>BU - Commercial Condo Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>TR - Townhouse Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>OI - Oilfield Improvements</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>AU - Agricultural Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>NV - Non-Valued Property</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>RU - Residential Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>FR - Farmstead Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>MR - Mixed Use / Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>LA - Locally Assessed Utility</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>CA - Centrally Assessed</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>CR - Commercial Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>CU - Commercial Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>IU - Industrial Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>KR - Condominium Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>TP - Tribal Property</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>KU - Condominium Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>FU - Farmstead Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>TU - Townhouse Urban</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>RR - Residential Rural</edomv></edom><edom><edomv>VU - Vacant Land Urban</edomv></edom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="TRUE">PropType</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">60</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">OwnerAddre</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">OwnerAddre</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">64</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">OwnerAdd_1</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">OwnerAdd_1</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">64</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">OwnerAdd_2</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">OwnerAdd_2</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">64</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>Shape_Area</attrlabl><attrdef>Area of feature in internal units squared.</attrdef><attrdefs>Esri</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom>Positive real numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv><attalias Sync="TRUE">SHAPE_Area</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">TotalValue</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">TotalValue</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Integer</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">10</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">OwnerZipCo</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">OwnerZipCo</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">50</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">CareOfTaxp</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">CareOfTaxp</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">167</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl Sync="TRUE">SHAPE_Leng</attrlabl><attalias Sync="TRUE">SHAPE_Leng</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr><attr><attrlabl>PropertyID</attrlabl><attrdef>ORION database unique property ID number</attrdef><attalias Sync="TRUE">PropertyID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Integer</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">10</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr></detailed><overview><eaover>base attributes of taxable land parcels created during conversion. You may encounter other attributes but that means they have been added by the maintainer and were not part of the original data.</eaover></overview></eainfo><mdHrLvName Sync="TRUE">dataset</mdHrLvName><refSysInfo><RefSystem><refSysID><identCode code="32100" Sync="TRUE"/><idCodeSpace Sync="TRUE">EPSG</idCodeSpace><idVersion Sync="TRUE">4.5(3.0.1)</idVersion></refSysID></RefSystem></refSysInfo><spatRepInfo><VectSpatRep><geometObjs Name="BighornOwnerParcel_shp"><geoObjTyp><GeoObjTypCd value="002" Sync="TRUE"></GeoObjTypCd></geoObjTyp><geoObjCnt Sync="TRUE">0</geoObjCnt></geometObjs><topLvl><TopoLevCd value="001" Sync="TRUE"></TopoLevCd></topLvl></VectSpatRep></spatRepInfo><spdoinfo><ptvctinf><esriterm Name="BighornOwnerParcel_shp"><efeatyp Sync="TRUE">Simple</efeatyp><efeageom code="4" Sync="TRUE"></efeageom><esritopo Sync="TRUE">FALSE</esritopo><efeacnt Sync="TRUE">0</efeacnt><spindex Sync="TRUE">FALSE</spindex><linrefer Sync="TRUE">FALSE</linrefer></esriterm></ptvctinf></spdoinfo></metadata>
